I am NOT one of these guys who pays a
whole lot of attention to global warming
and things like that I'll be honest I
really don't care about those kind of
things and I'm pretty sure that's
because I have two teenage daughters
anybody out there with teenage daughters
I'm sure you'll back me up when I say it
yeah I'm sure you'll back me up when I
say that there are a lot of days where I
really don't care what kind of planet
they're left way there
teenage girls huh
you know there's time there's times I
don't even like it when they call me dad
it just just implies a level of
commitment I'm not always up for just
Thursday's they approach and I just
stopped them about 10 feet away you know
what I'm Dave today Dave doesn't have
$20 Dave can't drive you to Maddie's
house with any luck your dad will be
back in a couple days that's all I can
tell you the way they talked is just so
sharp and just so angry ask my oldest
start I said what do you want to do with
your life she goes I like birds did you
even hear the question I asked you she
goes yeah I like birds I want to be an
ornithologist all right so she's not
moving out
I love them the man I love I love having
kids and I can remember when they were
little you know that first one the first
one scares you to death don't think us
that's when you prepare for you /
prepare you read books you watch videos
you go to class you think you know
everything the water breaks you forget
everything Mary the first time I held my
oldest daughter in the hospital she
pooped her diaper I thought she was
gonna blow like a potato in the
microwave cuz if you've ever seen an
infant do that they squeezed into a tiny
lumpy and I'm screaming at my wife get a
fork put some Bulls hair if this kid
blows the insurance does not cover the
cleanup I'll guarantee it
but then you get him home you get to
figure him out at home don't you you get
to close the door you all right let's
see what we got here you figure out
they're a lot more durable than you
thought which is great training for the
second kit because by the time the
second kid rolls around you're a pro
you're so much more confident with your
second child because by that time you've
been pooped on peed on puked on you've
used your own finger to dig a booger out
of somebody else's nose
so that second kid you don't even really
care about that second kid do you mean
they're naked rolling and dirt in the
backyard
hoser off we're late let's go they could
be going towards the outlet with a fork
you don't even stop him let's see what
happens
hey did you know that drive our comedy
has their own app download it right now
to watch save and share clips and watch
my whole special